exporters.sg 2005-12-10

# Exporters.com.sg - Privacy Statement

Exporters.SG is committed to protect your privacy. These following information tells you about our privacy policy and how we make use of the information collected from you.

Our Privacy Statement covers the following areas:

| 

> **1\. Information Collection & Use**
> 
> **2\. Information Sharing & Disclosures**
> 
> **3\. How You Can Choose To Opt Out**
> 
> **4\. How We Use Log Files**
> 
> **5\. What Is Cookies And How We Use It**

| 

> **6\. About Links to Other Sites**
> 
> **7\. About Discussion Boards/Chat Rooms**
> 
> **8\. Security Of Your Personal Information**
> 
> **9\. Business Transitions**
> 
> **10\. Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
  
---|---  
  
**1\. Information Collection & Use**

> **Membership Application  
>  **In order to be a member of Exporters.SG, you must first complete the membership application form. During application, you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 
> 
> As a member, you will received regular email newsletters (Exporters' Despatch and Trade Network Newsletters). In addition, you will also received email announcements on our service updates.
> 
> UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected on Exporters.SG. UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on Exporters.SG.
> 
> **Orders**  
>  If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 
> 
> We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
> 
> **Surveys**  
>  We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).
> 
> **Referrals**  
>  If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about Exporters.SG, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
> 
> **Newsletters**  
>  If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “How You Can Choose To Opt Out” section.
> 
> **Service-related Announcements  
>  **We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. Please see “How You Can Choose To Opt Out” section.
> 
> **Member Support**  
>  Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email containing your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.
> 
> **Profile**  
>  We store information that we collect through cookies, log files to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to improve the content of the Exporters.SG for you.

**2\. Information Sharing & Disclosures**

> **Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
>  **We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.
> 
> **Personally identifiable information  
>  **We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties that are not publicly available in Exporters.SG. For example, your email address.
> 
> We do share your company information that is publicly available like company name, company address, business description and contact numbers with trade promoting organisations. For instance [IE Singapore](http://www.iesingapore.com/), [Austrade](http://www.austrade.com.sg/). The purpose of sharing these information is to give a better exposures for our members.
> 
> **Agents  
>  **We use these online payment processing companies (WorldPay Ltd and PayPal) to bill you for goods and services. These company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
> 
> **Service Providers**
> 
>   * **Payment Processing**  
>  We use these online payment processing companies (WorldPay Ltd and PayPal) to bill you for goods and services. These company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
>   * **Member Authentication and Verification**  
>  We use other third parties to provide authentication and verification of members on our site. When you sign up for Member Authentication and Verification service, we will share information on your company name, address and contact information as necessary for the third party to provide this service.
>   * **Escrow**  
>  We integrate Escrow.com service into Exporters.SG to allow members to transact safely. Please refer to Escrow.com [privacy policy](https://www.escrow.com/resources/privacy_policy.asp) for more information.
> 

> 
> **Legal Disclaimer  
> ** We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Exporters.SG.

**3\. How You Can Choose To Opt Out**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter communication or contact us.

**4\. How We Use Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information so that we can provide this information to third-parties in case of fraud and crime.

**5\. What Is Cookies And How We Use It**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. 

We use persistent cookie when you want Exporters.SG to remember your email address for your log in. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

**6\. About Links to Other Sites**

Exporters.SG contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd. Please be aware that we, UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Exporters.SG. 

**7\. About Discussion Boards/Chat Rooms**

If you use a discussion board or chat room on Exporters.SG, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**8\. Security Of Your Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

**9\. Business Transitions**

In the event UNET Global Solutions Pte Ltd goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on Exporters.SG of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**10\. Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Updated on 4th October 2005**
